A Guide to the Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection, 1976-1986 (bulk 1985-1986)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection, 1976-1986 (bulk 1985-1986)
Fairfax County Public Library
2023.007
0.5 linear feet
The Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection consists of 35mm negatives featuring 1,516 images dating from 1976-1986.
Fairfax County, Virginia, Office of Comprehensive Planning, Heritage Resources Branch
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Collection transferred by the Fairfax County Department of Planning and Development in March 2023.
Historical and Biographical Information
In early 1985, the Fairfax County Heritage Resources Branch hired two grant staff, Betsy Chittenden, an architectural historian, and Andrea Heintzelman, a survey archaeologist, to assist them with conducting a survey of the western part of Fairfax County. By the end of February 1985, the two had completed the survey’s research design and began working on the physical survey. Upon conclusion of the grant on August 30, 1985, Chittenden and Heintzelman surveyed and photographed 113 structures mostly in the Chantilly, Virginia vicinity and assisted staff with writing the Western Fairfax County Survey Report. The report documented and interpreted the architectural history of the area and made recommendations for preservation strategies and future research suggestions.
Scope and Content
The Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection consists of 35mm negatives featuring 1,516 images dating from 1976-1986. The bulk of the images were photographed during the 1985 grant-funded survey of the western area of Fairfax County and were published in the report co-authored by grant staff Betsy Chittenden and Andrea Heintzelman. Several negatives in this collection both pre-date and post date the survey project. Images depict farms, barns, houses, schools, churches and other historic structures in the Chantilly area of Fairfax County, Virginia. Many of these sites no longer exist and have been overtaken by development.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
Index Terms
Centreville (Va.) - History; Chantilly (Va.) - History; Chittenden, Betsy; David, Elizabeth S., 1939-2022.; Fairfax (Va.) - History; Fairfax County (Va.). Office of Comprehensive Planning. Heritage Resources Branch; Falls Church (Va.) - History; Floris (Va.) - History; Heintzelman, Andrea; Herndon (Va.) - History; Historic sites - Virginia - Fairfax County; Vienna (Va.) - History
Container List
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields #1, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A2, Westfields #2, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A2, Westfields #2, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A2, Westfields #2, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A2, Westfields #2, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A2, Westfields #2, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 March 21; Roll #: 85-1, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A1, Bradley Farms #1, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A1, Bradley Farms #1, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A1, Bradley Farms #1, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A1, Bradley Farms #1, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 March 27; Roll #: 85-2, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 38-4-A1, Springfield (Broadwater), 1985 March 31; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 55-4-A1, Log House, 1985 April 2; Roll #: 85-3, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A1, Martin House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A1, Martin House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A1, Martin House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A1, Martin House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 15-4-H12, Abandoned Ox Road, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 15-4-H12, Abandoned Ox Road, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A1, Waggle House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A1, Waggle House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A1, Waggle House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A1, Waggle House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A1, Waggle House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A1, Waggle House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-4, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A3, Newman House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A2, Floris Colored School, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A2, Floris Colored School, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A5, Corum House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A5, Corum House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A4, Keyes House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A4, Keyes House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A4, Keyes House, 1985 April 23; Roll #: 85-5, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A4, Keyes House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A4, Keyes House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A1, Martin House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A1, Martin House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 15-4-A6, Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: no site, Miscellaneous on Coppermine Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: no site, Miscellaneous on Coppermine Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A1, Herndon Church of God, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A1, Herndon Church of God, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, House at 2528 Centreville Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, House at 2516 Centreville Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A2, House at 2512 Centreville Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A2, House at 2512 Centreville Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A2, House at 2512 Centreville Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-6, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 35-1-A1, Wrenn House at Franklin Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A2, Bradley Farms #2, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-7, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, Gearhart House - 2630 Centreville Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, Gearhart House - 2630 Centreville Road, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-8, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A3, Barn, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A3, Barn, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A3, Barn, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A3, Barn, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A3, Barn, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 25-3-A3, Barn, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 21-1-A2, Frying Pan Baptist Church, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A3, Bowman's Store, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 24-2-A1, Middleton Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-9, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-10, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 44-4-A1, Westfields Log House, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A1, James Farm, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 43-2-A2, Farmington (Scott) Cemetery, 1985 April; Roll #: 85-11, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: no site, 2707 Centreville Road, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: no site, 2705 Centreville Road, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: no site, 2703 Centreville Road, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A16, Mullins House, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A17, Frying Pan Country Store, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A1, House, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-4-A2, House, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Ohgren House, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A3, Mills Farm, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-4-A1, Wrenn House under demolition, 1986 April 26; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-12, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A5, McNair Tenant House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A20, Hoffman House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A20, Hoffman House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 25-1-A20, Hoffman House, 1985 May; Roll #: 85-13, Frame #: 011